Sample Problem (Solid of Revolution - Volume - Standard)
Find the volume of one box of cigarettes
Don't do it.
Smoking's not allowed
on school grounds.
Clubs don't meet
during exam period, right?
I run every day
so I don't get out of shape.
Wow. And what do you do
for strength training?
I just run.
Really? And you're that jacked?
What?
You just run?
I just run.
You run?
That's it.
Maybe I'll go for a run, too.
You can't smoke off
school grounds, either.
A New Discovery!
A Study Session After School!!
Double-check your work
if you're done.
Okay, stop.
Turn your tests in from the back.
There's only one more day of exams,
but don't relax just yet.
1st Period: English
2nd Period:
Japanese History
3rd Period:
Physics
I worked real hard
on tomorrow's math test.
Huh? Dude, I just can't with math.
I suck at math.
Man, I'm beat. Guess I'll go
study in the library.
Borrow up to
2 books for 2 weeks
I knew it'd be crowded.
There aren't any open tables.
Guess I'll study at home.
Nakamura. Nakamura!
H-Hirose?
Sit here.
N-Next to him?
I'll be sitting next to Hirose?
Welcome!
Really? Is that really okay?
Excuse me.
You studying for exams, too?
Y-Yeah. You, too?
He's too close.
Yeah. He came crying to me
and asked to see my notes.
Oh, I see.
It's not like taking notes now will help.
Y-Yeah, it's just a stopgap.
A what?
Huh? A-A stopgap.
A last-minute temporary fix.
I've never heard that word before.
If you're good at modern Japanese,
maybe you can teach me.
What? U-Uh, sure. If you're okay with that.
Thanks, Senpai.
Am I going to die tomorrow?
Borrow up to
2 books for 2 weeks
Th-This isn't good.
I'm too distracted by Hirose to focus.
Ha...
"Ha"?
Dig a grave (Hakaana)
Ha... "Hakaana"?
To dig a grave.
He's so adorable.
What's next? Ah, "kinsen."
Touch heartstrings
Ko...
"Ko"?
Kotose
n
Kotosen?
No, stop. Focus on studying.
Hey, are you guys hungry?
I'm too hungry to focus.
Yeah, I guess. We haven't had lunch yet.
Wanna get some bread?
Isn't the school store closed today?
Aw, what? But I'm starving to death.
Should we go to
that new family restaurant?
Great idea! Let's go there now.
Sounds good. Let's go.
What? Really?
They're leaving already?
Hey.
Let's go, Nakamura.
Okay!
Restaurant
Man, I'm stuffed.
Th-This is my first time coming to
this kind of restaurant without my family.
Now that I've eaten, I'm sleepy.
I was so nervous,
I couldn't taste my food.
Right?
Did you see yesterday's
Detective Bari Kata?
Yeah, it was so good.
Did you see it, Hirose?
From the side. My family watched it.
The protagonist is so cool.
Huh? What are they talking about?
I only care about the female lead.
Do you watch that show?
Uh, a little of it.
My sister's really into it.
It's super popular right now.
R-Really?
I like that actress.
Yeah, I bet you do.
Yeah, she looks like Hamaoka.
Crap! I have no clue what it is!
I'll look it up later!
No, she doesn't.
Yuuka-chan is way cuter.
Scribble, scribble.
Oh, nice. I like this song.
Oh, really?
It's all you listen to.
What? Really?
Didn't you borrow their album
from Ohmori the other day?
What? Really?
We're going to a concert soon.
What?! Really?!
Wait. With Ohmori?
I'm so jealous! I want to go
to a concert with just Hirose!
Nakamura, do you have any favorite music?
Uh, I-I listen to everything.
Really?
When I'm into something,
it's all I listen to.
I'm into this band called Aquapet.
Do you know them?
Uh, sure.
Whoa! There's a SmaFi update!
What? Let me see.
C'mon! Can't I come up
with anything better than that?
What's in it?
There's a bunch of new levels!
Oh, dang. We should play.
Let's meet at Yoshida's place
when exams are over.
I can't wait. Let's play now.
I know the exams are easy
for you, but screw you.
You're the only one who's in trouble.
Hey, should we wager something?
On the exams?
No.
Nakamura.
Smash Fighter. It's really big right now.
Do you know it?
Y-Yeah, I do. It's popular, right?
Though I actually haven't played it yet.
Really? It's fun. You should try it.
Is SmaFi popular?
This is a starter level. Nice.
I lied. I just learned about it.
I love this weapons update.
Huh? What's your current rating?
Smash Fighter, was it?
I'll look it up later.
Around 70?
You'll get one-shotted.
Nah, don't underestimate me.
I'm all out right now.
What? You play too much.
I'm getting a drink.
Want anything, Nakamura?
Oh, u-uh...
I'll take a cola.
Ginger ale for me.
Seriously, guys?
I'll go with you.
Sorry for making you come with me.
Oh, it's okay. It'd be hard
to carry four cups.
There's that, too.
But I thought maybe you wanted
to study quietly by yourself.
What?
Oh, no. No, no, no.
What am I doing?
I'm making Hirose worry about me.
And I still don't know anything
about Hirose.
Nakamura, you like coffee?
Uh, y-yeah. I guess I drink a lot of it.
Huh. It's not really my thing.
Oh, but I like café au lait.
Y-Yeah, that's good, too.
Hirose can't drink black coffee?
That tracks.
Oh, my sister says it's good
with hot chocolate.
R-Really? Maybe I'll try that.
Well? Is it good?
Yeah, it's pretty good.
Maybe I'll try it next time.
Yeah, I think you could drink this.
I'm putting something in my drink, too.
I didn't know about this, either.
I know. Let's put coffee
in Takeuchi's cola.
What?
Don't tell him.
Hirose likes to pull pranks, too?
Thanks for waiting.
Took you long enough.
Sorry.
Thanks.
What were you doing?
Shut up. Get your own drink, then.
Thanks.
Detective Bari Kata?
Watches with family
TV show
Sister is really
into it
Currently popular
Favorite music!
Listens to only
this?!
Borrows albums
from Ohmori
Going to
a concert
soon
With Ohmori?!
So jealous
Aquapet!
Smash Fighter
Mobile game,
currently super popular
Seriously? Why?
I learned a lot about Hirose today.
There's so much I don't know about him.
Has cola always been this dark?
Maybe the color's different
because it's sugar-free.
If you don't want it,
why don't you get a new one?
Dude, gross.
What? I-It was that bad?
What did you...
I'm filming this.
Sorry. Do you want another?
Like hell I do!
Bye, Sensei.
Bye. Take care on the way home.
Okay.
Oh, Niou-sensei. You're always running.
Yes. To stay in shape.
Don't overdo it.
Beautiful.
What?
Oh, you noticed? Aren't they pretty?
They bloomed today.
They're called cyclamen,
and they bloom in the colder months.
Niou-sensei, do you like flowers?
There are other pretty flowers, too.
I'll display them sometime.
Well, I'll see you later.
Oh, I'm sorry for stopping you.
See you tomorrow.
Uh-huh. I see how it is.
We're still a long way from spring.
Hey, get off me.
Why? We're in love, aren't we?
That was something I just blurted out.
I don't know what love is.
This is the love story
of two lunches
This is the love story of two lunches.
Don't worry. I'll show you
exactly what love is.
M-Makunouchi...
Then, a rival appears.
A rival
appears
A-Are you...
Who?
What will be the fate of their love?
Makunouchi! Makunouchi!
Makunouchi!
Taku! I'll be the one to microwave you!
I won't let anyone else microwave you.
Lovable Lunches!
Anime greenlit!!!
Anime greenlit!
If you get too warm, you'll explode.
Lovable Lunches!
Anime greenlit!!!
Super Exciting!
Lovable Lunches Autograph Signing!!
The day has finally arrived.
Lovable Lunches!
I've been reading it
ever since middle school.
No, since the series started.
My favorite storylines are, uh...
First, there's Makunouchi's confession
and the elusive special.
There's also Taku's homemade juice.
Oh, and their awakening to new flavors.
Ah, I could go on about it forever.
The day has finally arrived.
I've been looking forward
to this since forever.
Today's the Lovable Lunches anime
green-lighting autograph session!
Lovable Lunches!
Long-awaited
TV anime
greenlit!
Lovable Lunches!
Anime Green-Lighting & New Volume Release
Kometani Ii-sensei Autograph Session
Date: 11/10 (Sun)
Location: Animate Ikebukuro Main Store
Time: Starts 2:30PM
Apply Here — Tickets Required
Lovable Lunches!
Kometani Ii
Volume 5
on sale
now!
Hifumi.
Have you decided?
Ah, sorry. Give me another minute.
Could I get this, please?
Is this for you?
It's a gift.
Sorry about that.
That took forever.
Now, now. We have plenty of time.
Let's get some tea.
In that case, there's somewhere
I'd like to go. Is that okay?
Lovable Lunches!
Oh, wow! I've never been
to a collab café before.
Lovable Lunches!
Right? Isn't it amazing?
Whoa, they perfectly recreated
Taku's lunch from volume 4.
What are you getting?
Heartfelt
Riceball Lunch
Special Lovebirds
Character Lunch
Heart-Melting
Sweet Lunch
Holy Lunchbox Academy
French Toast Sandwiches
Sigh of Relief
Makunouchi Green Tea
Taku's Homemade
Ginger Ale
Heart-Pounding
Love Lunch
Lovable Lunches!
Hmm, I'm interested in the Sigh of Relief
Makunouchi Green Tea.
And Taku's Homemade Ginger Ale.
I'm getting a sandwich.
Then, I'll get a character lunch.
What about you, Hifumi?
I can't decide.
Everything looks good, but I think
I'll get the Heart-Pounding Love Lunch.
Then, let's order.
Excuse me.
Coming.
Hifumi, could you order for us?
What?
What can I get you?
Holy Lunchbox Academy
French Toast Sandwiches
Sand-
wiches
are
supreme...
Could we get
the Holy Lunchbox
Academy French
Toast Sandwiches,
the "Special Lovebirds"
Character Lunch,
"Special Lovebirds"
Character Lunch
Comes With Original Coaster!
and "Taku-kun and Makunouchi-kun's
Heart-Pounding Love Lunch"?
Heart-Pounding
Love Lunch
Whatever...
It's all
leftovers.
Aw, he's
so easily
embarr-
assed.
So one French toast sandwich,
one character lunch, and one love lunch.
Is that right?
Y-Yes.
Thanks.
You probably could've
shortened the names.
Hey, get off me.
Why? We're in love, aren't we?
Wow, they're really moving and talking.
I'm glad you got a ticket.
Yeah, you really love Lovable Lunches.
I'll finally get to see their awakening
to new flavors animated.
Thanks for coming
all the way here with me.
It's fine. We wanted
to come to Animate, too.
By the way, did you finish
writing your letter?
Y-Yeah. It took all night
since there was so much I wanted to write.
I'm so excited.
Thank you for waiting.
This actually looks good.
The portions are big.
Right?
These are too cute to eat.
Lovable Lunches
Congrats on the Anime
City bookstores are
on another level! Wow!
TV Anime Greenlit!
Lovable Lunches!
Breaking
News
TV Anime Greenlit!!!!!
It's finally being animated.
I'll get to see their awakening
to new flavors animated.
Hey, get off me.
Why? We're in love, aren't we?
Th-That was something I just blurted out.
I don't know what love is.
Don't worry. I'll show you
exactly what love is.
N-Nakamura...
Uh, excuse me.
I'd like to grab one of those.
S-S-S-Sorry!
Crap, crap, crap.
Lovable Lunches!
Kometani Ii-sensei
Anime Green-Lighting
& New Volume Release
Autograph Session
Date: 11/10 (Sun)
Location: Animate Ikebukuro Main Store
Time: Starts 2:30PM
Lovable Lunches' Kometani Ii-sensei's
autograph session.
I didn't think I'd get a ticket.
But somehow, I did.
Lovable Lunches! Autograph Session Invitation
Celebrating the Anime Green-Lighting & New Volume Release
Kometani Ii-sensei
11/10 (Sun)
Animate Ikebukuro Main Store
Starts 2:30PM
[Not For Resale or Transfer]
This ticket is required to receive an autograph.
Do not forget to bring it with you.
Only the ticket holder may attend the autograph session.
Animate Ikebukuro
Main Store
My luck hasn't run out yet.
Detective Bari Kata is great, isn't it?
I love the actor who plays the lead.
I didn't think they'd cast
a Hollywood actor.
K-Kawamura-san? What's she doing here?
Huh? What is it?
I thought I saw someone looking at us.
It's nothing. Maybe I imagined it.
We're gonna check out the merch upstairs.
I'll head up once I'm finished down here.
Kawamura-san's by herself.
I should be able to hide until it's time.
Wh-What?! She's going to
the autograph session, too?
Lovable Lunches! Autograph Session Invitation
Celebrating the Anime Green-Lighting & New Volume Release
What should I do? Leave?
But I'm really looking forward to this.
The Lovable Lunches autograph session
will now begin.
Crud. It's time.
Ticket holders, please sign in and enter.
I'll have to use my ace in the hole.
Lovable Lunches!
Yup, good. This'll do for the time being.
Excuse me, sir.
Huh?
For security reasons, could you remove
that cloth on your face before entering?
Oh, a-actually, u-um...
May I see your ID as well?
What? Actually, uh...
Wow, there are all kinds
of people in the city.
You don't need to worry about me.
I'll be the judge of that.
Huh? That slouch...
And those eyes...
Badump
Nakamura-kun?
Thanks. Sorry about that, Kawamura-san.
It's totally fine.
I'm glad we were able to clear it up.
It's even more embarrassing
since she instantly knew it was me.
Anyway, I never expected
to run into you here.
You won a ticket, too, huh?
I-I should come clean.
I actually...
I-I...
I love Lovable Lunches!
What? Yeah, I know.
What? How?
You read it at school sometimes,
so I figured you liked it.
Oh, she already knew.
Sorry. Was that supposed to be a secret?
By the way, what's your favorite storyline?
What? Well, it's hard to choose.
I like Makunouchi's confession...
Ah, that's a good one.
But my favorite's probably Taku and
Makunouchi's awakening to new flavors.
Right? That's my favorite storyline, too.
You, too?
Isn't it great?
It's so good. It's like
their feelings become one.
The autograph session will now begin.
Please follow the instructions
of the staff and move forward.
I'd better get ready.
What's that?
A letter. You don't get much time
at these events,
so I wrote down everything
I wanted to say.
Th-That's a brilliant idea!
It didn't occur to me to do that.
Wh-What's in the bag?
A gift. I had trouble
deciding what to get.
That's another brilliant idea!
Oh, you're not required
to bring anything. It's okay.
Okay.
Kometani Ii-sensei
Autograph Session
Here you go.
Thank you.
Next person, please.
It's almost our turn.
Yeah. I'm nervous.
The new volume was amazing.
Thanks. Here you go.
Thank you.
We get less time to talk than I thought.
I'll skip my thoughts on the special,
and just talk about Makunouchi's
confession and the new flavors.
Oh, but I want to talk about Taku, too.
Ah, I can't narrow down what I want to say!
I should've written a letter like Kawamura-san,
despite what she said.
Next person, please.
It's Kawamura-san's turn already?
I've been reading Lovable Lunches
since it started.
I have a letter and gift for you.
Thanks. Which character would you like?
Um, Makunouchi-kun, please.
Makunouchi-kun? Got it.
What? We get a drawing of a character?
Is that even allowed?
Here you go.
Thank you.
Next person, please.
What?
I l-l-love Lovable Lunches!
Uh, um... T-Taku-kun is really cute.
Thank you. I'm glad to hear you say that,
since I like Taku, too.
Would you like a drawing of Taku-kun?
Y-Yes.
You're a student, right?
What's your name?
Nakamura!
Nakamura-kun, huh?
Good luck.
Thank you.
Next person, please.
I'm a huge fan.
What a haul. I'm satisfied.
You bought way too much.
If you want something,
you have to jump on it.
Parents and merch won't be around forever.
How'd it go, Hifumi?
Yeah, it was fun.
Hey, are you listening to me?
To Kawamura-san!
Kometani Ii
I'm glad I got to attend the event
with Nakamura-kun.
I'll write a letter next time.
Go for it! Nakamura-kun!